<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata>
	<!--
		CDATA tags mean no need to escape special characters.
		Don't worry about spaces at the start/end. That gets trimmed.
	-->
	<!-- The title of this mod. -->
	<title><![CDATA[ RadiKal Sector ]]></title>
	<!--
		This mod's thread on subsetgames.com.
		If there's no thread yet, create one to announce your upcoming mod in the
		forum. Then paste the url here.
	-->
	<threadUrl><![CDATA[ https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/214/mv-radikal-sector-equipment-ships ]]></threadUrl>
	<!-- Your forum user name. -->
	<author><![CDATA[ Dj0z ]]></author>
	<version><![CDATA[ 5.86d ]]></version>
	<description>
<![CDATA[
A relatively small add-on for Multiverse 5.5.1, which adds a secret sector, many spicy augments (multi-ramming, fire-related, special hacking, repair, internal...), blue options, upgrades, sounds, visuals and combos!
Also features a few weapons and 4 ships (3 unlockable) with specific gimmicks.
The general theme is powerful but potentially dangerous (to you) experimental tech. More content coming soon!

****** CONTENT ******
	
	RadiKal sector:
-Find the reroute coordinates during normal gameplay or buy a double agent from a shop to get those, then reroute as usual.
-It's full of danger, sacrifices and rare, powerful equipment! Will you dare enter?

	Resource-hungry Combat Augments:
-Shipvore Ram: recklessly throw your ship at the enemy, disregarding your fuel reserves and the safety of your crew. 
Combos with Fuel Conserver and Emergency Generator.
-Scorched Earth, for when you want to set your own ship on fire, and benefit from it.
Comes with upgrades, streamlining the experience and empowering your crew.
-Plasma Teleporter: immediately ignite the enemy ship!
Comes with a safe and a risky deployment method.

	Other Offensive Augments:
-Flammabilizer: deal with fireproof and resistant enemies!
-Charged Belts makes your crew damage the ship they're in on death.
-Vulnerabilizer: slowly remove the enemy's defenses, with some randomness.

	Utility augments:
-Lead Titans: make your crew of specific races heavier, maybe too much for your ship.
-Enigmashin: gamble with fleet delays through briefly peaceful hacking.
-Oxygenizer: spawn an atmosphere at the start of fights.

	Defensive augments:
-Offense Disabler makes the enemy harmless for a few seconds, progressively restoring their power afterwards.
-Punk Harmony uses a bootleg Harmony to automate and empower your Engi, scaling with Mind Control and Hacking.
-Defense Kits make your crew much sturdier on your ship.
-A.E.R.A. Second Wind can automatically save your ship, once per purchase.

	Internal augments:
-Mind Heater: in fire, makes your crew resist Mind Control and stun, on both ships.
-Demicloners: provides a semblance of cloning when your crew dies without a Clonebay.

	Custom weapons:
-Bada fissure beam can deal massive damage to large systems, or blow up ships!
-Rain of Ions shoots all kinds of ions at once!
-Rain of Fire can eventually maintain multiple full strength fires against any ship!
-BPS Messenger heavy laser combines the strengths of all 3 RK subfactions.

	New crew:
-Uptors are made out of Alpha Gouls to fit the needs of the RK Scorch.

	Player ships with unique gimmicks!
-Embark on a wild ride with the Rammer, boasting a superior locked version of the Shipvore Ram.
-The Scorcher is outfitted with what you need to burn down any enemy.
-The Punker plays around its massive reactor, particle accelerator, and special hacking.


************ Changelog ******************
CHANGELOG RadiKal Sector v5.86d

-Improved some texts.
-Fixed some potential bugs where a few newer RK crew / items might not count for RK gear requirements.

* Augments
-New internal RK Punk augment "Mind Cooler": when mind controlled, your crew cannot fight, sabotage or teleport.
-Demicloners: internal requires droneparts instead of fuel, reduced scrap cost to compensate.
-Enigmashin: greyed out text now tells you if some choices are not available because your Hacking system is too weak.
-Offense Disabler: Fixed description saying it works on one artillery when actually it works on all of them.

* Crew
-Squyrt:
Now learns weapons even faster (max speed).
No longer shoots projectiles looking like itself.

* The RadiKal sector
-RK gear buyer unique beacons now allow storage actions if you don't engage in trading or combat.
-Stores now always sell at least 10 of each resource type. Reduced the max amount they can offer to compensate.


Special thanks to (in no particular order) Arc, Lizzard, codyfun, Qaser7, bamalf, Dr. Nauter, Witherbottom, Chooseche, Eschaton, Pepper, Untitled, Pupi, vertaalfout, Dalvest, Alder, Kix, [Enchanter], Pedrosian96, Royal Slime, [yenlo]R4V3-0N, robinthedragon2, Ehtya (Laythe), Blizz/mr_easy_money, Skye[NikoMaster], Julk, Felipe, marcrusian, Abstrusity and other people who helped on the FTL:MV Discord, for streaming the mod, and valuable information on balance, modding, coding and art.

Feedback? Questions? @Dj0z in the Multiverse server on Discord

Good luck and have fun!
]]>
</description>
</metadata>
