<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<metadata>
	<!--
		CDATA tags mean no need to escape special characters.
		Don't worry about spaces at the start/end. That gets trimmed.
	-->
	<!-- The title of this mod. -->
	<title><![CDATA[ RadiKal Sector ]]></title>
	<!--
		This mod's thread on subsetgames.com.
		If there's no thread yet, create one to announce your upcoming mod in the
		forum. Then paste the url here.
	-->
	<threadUrl><![CDATA[ https://ftlmultiverse.boards.net/thread/214/mv-radikal-sector-equipment-ships ]]></threadUrl>
	<!-- Your forum user name. -->
	<author><![CDATA[ Dj0z ]]></author>
	<version><![CDATA[ 5.93b ]]></version>
	<description>
<![CDATA[
(Patching: put Forgotten Races above RK to avoid populating their stores.)

An add-on for FTL: Multiverse v5.5.1, which adds a secret sector, multiple spicy augments (multi-ramming, extensive fire effects, special hacking, repair, internal...), including upgrades and combos!
Also features a few weapons and 5 ships (4 unlockable) with specific gimmicks.
The general theme is powerful but potentially dangerous (to you) experimental tech. More content coming soon!

****** CONTENT ******
	
The secret RadiKal sector:
-Weapons, augments and some other things are rarely accessible from the outside.
-Get coordinates rarely during normal play or from double agents in stores, then reroute. There might be other ways too.
-Original content, events, enemies, quests and specialized shops.
-Danger everywhere. You might trade crew, gear, reputation or something else for even better things. Will you dare?

Resource-hungry Combat Augments:
-Shipvore Ram: recklessly throw your ship at the enemy for heavy damage and repairs, risking your resources and more.
Keep the risks under control with experience, or intuition! Combos with Fuel Conserver and Emergency Generator.
-Offense Disabler makes the enemy harmless for a few seconds, progressively restoring their power afterwards.
-Vulnerabilizer: slowly remove the enemy's defenses, with some randomness.
-Plasma Teleporter: Light many fires on the enemy ship instantly!
Has safe and risky deployment methods. Combos with other augments.

Other offensive Augments:
-Charged Belts adds on-death damage and fire to your crew, stacking with similar effects. Has combo.
-Flammabilizer: deal with fireproof and resistant enemies or eradicate vulnerable ones!

Other defensive augments:
-Persistence Shield gives Super Shields, a way to recharge them instantly, and regular shield recharge speed!
-Thicker Hull can negate low damage hits, and always reduces high damage ones, with a drawback.
-Punk Harmony uses a bootleg Harmony to automate and empower your Engi, scaling with Mind Control and Hacking.
-Defense Kits make your crew much sturdier on your ship.
-A.E.R.A. Second Wind can automatically save your ship, once per purchase.

Utility augments:
-Lead Titans: make specific races stronger and heavier, maybe too much for your ship.
Others get repair and movement bonuses.
-Enigmashin: gamble with fleet delays through brief special hacking, maybe with consequences...
-Oxygenizer: spawn an atmosphere at the start of fights.
-Scorched Earth lets you set your rooms or ship on fire and benefit from it.
Upgradable. Combo with Plasma Teleporter.
-Surveyor: deep-search empty beacons for random loot.

Internal augments:
-Choking F.I.N.E.: protects from suffocation and gives boosts while suffocating.
-Demicloners: provides a semblance of cloning when your crew dies without a Clonebay.
-Mind Cooler: greatly reduces the impact of having your crew mind controlled.
-Hellion Wraps: in fire, your crew is combat boosted.
-Mind Heater: in fire, makes your crew resist Mind Control and stun, and also reveal adjacent rooms.

Efficient weapons:
-'Bada' fissure beam can deal massive damage to large systems, or blow up ships!
-'Unloader' can quickly throw your whole stock of missiles at the enemy.
-'Shotphaser' shotguns accelerated phase ions with high stun.
-'Rain of Ions' shoots all kinds of ions at once!
-'Rain of Fire' can eventually maintain full strength fires against any ship!
-'BPS Messenger' heavy laser combines the strengths of all 3 RK subfactions.

New crew:
-Squyrts are RK Bam modified Technopaths specialized in destruction.
-Uptors are made out of Alpha Gouls to fit the fiery needs of the RK Scorch.
-Unique crew!

Player ships with unique gimmicks!
-Embark on a wild ride with the Rammer, boasting a superior locked version of the Shipvore Ram.
-The Punker plays around its massive reactor, particle accelerator, and special hacking.
-The Scorcher is outfitted with what you need to burn down any enemy.


************ Changelog ******************
CHANGELOG RadiKal Sector v5.93b

-Improved some texts.
-Removed blurriness of an achievement image.
-Added RK main menu splash to the random possibilities. In theory. I haven't seen it yet.

* Rammer cruiser
-Layout B:
Fixed warning when starting the run that "the ship isn't made for Multiverse" caused by missing hidden augment that identifies it as one.
Fixed it not counting as RK Bam gear, which would never be a problem since it has a locked RK Bam augment.
Fixed it not counting as an RK ship for Tully S8 text.

* Punker cruiser
-Fixed layout A counting as RK Bam gear instead of RK Punk.

* Crew
-Squyrt: now capable of sabotage.


Special thanks to (in no particular order) Zuggo, LoudMute, Arc, Lizzard, codyfun, Qaser7, bamalf, Dr. Nauter, Witherbottom, Chooseche, Eschaton, Pepper, Untitled, Pupi, vertaalfout, Dalvest, Alder, Kix, [Enchanter], Pedrosian96, Royal Slime, [yenlo]R4V3-0N, robinthedragon2, Ehtya (Laythe), Blizz/mr_easy_money, Skye[NikoMaster], Julk, Felipe, marcrusian, Abstrusity and other people who helped on the FTL:MV Discord, for streaming the mod, and valuable information on balance, modding, coding and art.

Feedback? Questions? @Dj0z in the Multiverse server on Discord

Good luck and have fun!
]]>
</description>
</metadata>
